Power cords ring out, as I sit at my desk Riffing the daydreams, running through my head Scrolling the endless, feed for some delight Online I'm loud, offline I stay out of sight Boot up my day, I'm ready to post Snap a new pic, filter it the most
Followers climb, but I'm stuck in my room.
IRL me is out of tune.
Spring name is Fall.
My avatar's cool, like by a crowd I never met at school.
DMs are fire.
Replies coming fast, but real conversations never last.
I tour online, that's what my group boss says.
Got the quip it whines, and a thousand friends.
IRL I'm weird, can't look them in the eye.
But I've imagined, me I buy wi-fi.
Type it up, it says, feel alive, I tour online.
I'm fuller on mine Photoshop friend I'm livin' the meme Scrollin' content I know what I mean Laughing emoji To cover the pain I'll find my jokes Don't land the same
I just dream of everything I want to be, but face to face I always freeze.
I'm taller online, that's what my papa says.
Got the perfect ones, and a thousand friends.
I are out of words, I can't look that in the eye.
But I've a legend behind my back L, L it's I, I'm not fine, I'm four on nine, four on nine